STANISLAVA GEORGIEVA

Junior Front-End Developer

+359878779859 @ miss_stanislava@yahoo.com

https://stanislava-georgieva-portfolio.com/

ttps://www.linkedin.com/in/stanislava-georgieva-71686128a/

SUMMARY

I am an enthusiastic professional ready to make a career switch into front-end development. I have a strong passion for creating intuitive and engaging user experiences and have focused on mastering JavaScript and other essential skills for this role. Along with my technical knowledge, I bring valuable soft skills such as excellent problem-solving abilities, effective communication, and a collaborative team mindset. I am highly adaptable, a quick learner, and have a keen eye for detail. This career change is driven by my deep passion for technology and innovation. I am excited to apply my skills in front-end development .

EDUCATION

React.js - The complete guide (Next.js,Redux)

07/2024

Udemy

JavaScript Program - Alpha

01/2024 - 06/2024

Telerik Academy

- Core Topics: JavaScript core, OOP, Data structures and algorithms, JavaScript web, Client-side apps, React.js
- Achievements: Excellent scores on every progress review, recognized as one of the best students in the program

B.Sc. Finance 09/2001 - 05/2005

Bourgas Free University

PROJECTS

Event Calendar- Team project

05/2024

Telerik Academy

https://github.com/Event-calendar-Final-Project/Event-Calendar-Final-Project-A58

 Developed an Event Calendar app with ReactJS as a single-page application. Utilized the DOM API for dynamic content manipulation. Use firebase authentification.

Forum - Team project

04/2024

Telerik Academy

https://github.com/Forum-Project-Team-8/Forum

Giphy - Team Project

03/2024

Telerik Academy

https://github.com/Web-project-A58/Web-project-A58

EXPERIENCE

Technical Assistant

10/2016 - 10/2023

DDD 1TLD

Burgas

Leader in service sales

Sales expert

05/2012 - 10/2016

ESTIL LTD

Burgas

Sales



SKILLS

Javascript * ReactJS * HTML * CSS * GitHub * Node.js

LANGUAGES

English

Proficient



TRAINING / COURSES

Proficient in graphic design, with expertise in CorelDRAW, Photoshop, and Adobe Illustrator.

Skilled in Information and Communication Technologies, particularly adept with the Microsoft Office suite.

PASSIONS

- Travel- exploring new cultures and discovering hidden gems.
- Photography Passionate about photography for its power to freeze moments and tell untold stories.

MY LIFE PHILOSOPHY

Import (dreams) from './life'

while(alive) {

dreams.chase(everyday)

giveUp.never()

}

— JS

EXPERIENCE

Technical Assistant
DIP GROUP LTD

Construction of pools and spa centers

04/2007 - 10/2011

Burgas